A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1966-1967
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1966-1967
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.701
This collection consists of 37,200 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 3 September 1970.
Scope and Content Information
These files constitute the major record series generated by the president of the University of Virginia. The records consist chiefly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office.
Contents List
- General Files, 1966-1967
  - "A - Am" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 1)
  - "An - Az" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 1)
  - Academic Deans 1966-1967 (Box 1)
  - Adams Papers 1966-1967 (Box 1)
  - Admissions - General 1966-1967 (Box 1)
  - Admissions - Applicants 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Admissions - Reports 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Advisory Panel on ROTC Affairs 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Air Force Academy 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Air Force and Air Force ROTC 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Albemarle County Public Schools 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Association - General 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Association - Delaware 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Association - Lynchburg 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Association - Medical 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Day 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Fund 1966-1967 (Box 3)
  - Alumni News 1966-1967 (Box 3)
  - American Association of University Professors 1966-1967 (Box 3)
  - American Council on Education 1966-1967 (Box 3)
  - Annual Reports 1966-1967 (Box 3)
  - Applications - "A" 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "B" 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "C" 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "D" 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "E" (folder empty) 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "F" (folder empty) 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "G" 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "H" 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "I" (folder empty) 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "J" 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "K" 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "L" 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "M" 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "N" 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "O" (folder empty) 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "P" 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "Q" (folder empty) 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "R" 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "S" 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "T" 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "U" (folder empty) 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "V" (folder empty) 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - "W" 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Applications - ""X - Y - Z" (folder empty) 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Architecture - General 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Architecture - Personnel 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Army - General 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Army - Judge Advocate General's (J. A. G.) School 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Army - Judge Advocate General's (J. A. G.) School Building 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Army - ROTC 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Art 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Art Commission 1966-1967 (Box 5)
  - Asian Studies Consortium 1966-1967 (Box 5)
  - Association of American Colleges 1966-1967 (Box 5)
  - Association of American Universities 1966-1967 (Box 5)
  - Astronomy 1966-1967 (Box 5)
  - Athletics - General 1966-1967 (Box 5)
  - Athletics - Personnel 1966-1967 (Box 6)
  - Athletics - ACC 1966-1967 (Box 6)
  - Athletics - Football: Wake Forest, 17 September 1966 1966-1967 (Box 6)
  - Athletics - Football: Tulane, 8 October 1966 - Commonwealth Day 1966-1967 (Box 6)
  - Athletics - Football: V. M. I., 15 October 1966 1966-1967 (Box 6)
  - Athletics - Football: V. P. I., 22 October 1966 1966-1967 (Box 6)
  - Athletics - Football: Maryland, 19 November 1966 1966-1967 (Box 6)
  - Athletics - Football: North Carolina, 26 November 1966 1966-1967 (Box 6)
  - Athletics - 3 -2- 2 Committee 1966-1967 (Box 6)
  - Athletics - Finances 1966-1967 (Box 6)
  - Athletics - Invitations to Games 1966-1967 (Box 6)
  - Athletics - NCAA 1966-1967 (Box 6)
  - Athletics - Atlantic Council of the U. S. 1966-1967 (Box 6)
  - Athletics - Atomic Energy Commission 1966-1967 (Box 6)
  - Audit Reports 1966-1967 (Box 7)
  - "B - Bm" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 7)
  - "Bn - Bz" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 7)
  - Berkeley, Francis L., Jr. 1966-1967 (Box 7)
  - Biology - Blandy Farm 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Biology - General 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Biology - Mountain Lake 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Budget - Capital Outlay 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Budget - Director's Office 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Budget - Miscellaneous Information 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Budget - Operating 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Building Program (see Department or Division concerned) 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Buildings and Grounds - General 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Buildings and Grounds - Progress Reports 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Bureau of Population and Economic Research 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Bursar - (Includes information on tuition, fees, employment benefits, etc.) 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - "Ca - Ck" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 9)
  - "Cl - Cz" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 9)
  - Calendar of Events 1966-1967 (Box 9)
  - Catholic Center 1966-1967 (Box 9)
  - Cavalier Daily 1966-1967 (Box 9)
  - Center for Advanced Studies in the Sciences Folder # 1 1966-1967 (Box 10)
  - Center for Advanced Studies in the Sciences Folder # 2 1966-1967 (Box 10)
  - Center for Urban Studies, Proposal 1966-1967 (Box 10)
  - Charlottesville, City of Housing Advisory Committee (file for Mr. Berkeley) 1966-1967 (Box 10)
  - Chemistry 1966-1967 (Box 10)
  - Chemistry Building 1966-1967 (Box 10)
  - Children's Rehabilitation Center (see also Rehabilitation Center) 1966-1967 (Box 10)
  - Civil Defense 1966-1967 (Box 10)
  - Civil Rights 1966-1967 (Box 10)
  - Clinch Valley College - Building Program 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Clinch Valley College - General 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Clinch Valley College - Personnel 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - College of Arts and Sciences 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - College Entrance Examination Board (see Admissions) 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Colonnade Club 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Commerce - General 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Commerce - Personnel 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee (ad hoc) - Advisory Committee on Personnel Practices 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee (ad hoc) - Clinical Psychology 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee (ad hoc) - Geology 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee (ad hoc) - Enrollment Projection 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee (ad hoc) - Religion Department - John B. Cary Memorial Professorship 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee (ad hoc) - Transfer Students from the Newly-Established Community Colleges 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee - Administrative 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee - Admissions 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee - Algernon Sydney Sullivan Award 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee - Architectural Advisory 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee - Athletic Advisory 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee - Blandy Farm Advisory 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee - Calendar and Scheduling 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee - Catalogue 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee - Cemetery 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee - Chapel 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee - Communications 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee - Computer Center 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee - Foreign Students 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee - Fraternities 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee - Future of the University 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee - Graduate 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee - Housing 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee - Institutional Analysis 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee - Lectures - Page, Barbour, Richard 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Committee - Law School Dean 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - Library 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - Master Plan 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - Medical Affairs Policy 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - Names 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - National Medal of Sciences 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - Placement 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - Processions 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - Public Occasions 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - Radiation Safety 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - Registration 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - Research 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - Research in the Humanities 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - ROTC Affairs 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - Scholarships, Grants-in-Aid, Loans, and Employment 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - Student Activities 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - Student Health 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - Teacher Education 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - Traffic Control 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - University Committee on Students 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - University Names Committee 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - University Press 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee - Wilson Gee Institute for Research in the Social Sciences 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee, Special - Academic Legislation 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee, Special - Admission Dean 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee, Special - Advisory Committee on Placement 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee, Special - Architecture Deanship 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee, Special - Biophysics 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee, Special - Central Utilities, Long-Range Planning 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee, Special - Clinch Valley College, Women's Dorm. 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee, Special - Engineering and Applied Science, School of (addition) 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee, Special - George Mason Advisory 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee, Special - Chancellor for George Mason College 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee, Special - Educational Planning for George Mason College 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee, Special - Heating Plant Alterations and Additions 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee, Special - International Studies and Research 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee, Special - Social Needs and Facilities 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Committee, Special - Nursing School Building 1966-1967 (Box 13)
  - Committee, Special - Orientation 1966-1967 (Box 13)
  - Committee, Special - Patrick Henry Advisory 1966-1967 (Box 13)
  - Committee, Special - Reactor Safety 1966-1967 (Box 13)
  - Committee, Special - Rehabilitation Center Building 1966-1967 (Box 13)
  - Committee, Special - Sesquicentennial 1966-1967 (Box 13)
  - Committee, Special - Study on the Admission of Women 1966-1967 (Box 13)
  - Committee, Special - Tree 1966-1967 (Box 13)
  - Committee, Special - Washington Papers 1966-1967 (Box 13)
  - Committee, Special - Selection of Dean of Women 1966-1967 (Box 13)
  - Community Colleges 1966-1967 (Box 13)
  - Comptroller 1966-1967 (Box 13)
  - Computer Center 1966-1967 (Box 13)
  - Copeley Hill - Married Student Housing 1966-1967 (Box 13)
  - Council of Presidents 1966-1967 (Box 13)
  - Council of Southern Universities (see also Southern Fellowships Fund) 1966-1967 (Box 13)
  - Counseling Center 1966-1967 (Box 13)
  - "Da - De" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 14)
  - "Df - Dz" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 14)
  - Darden, C. W., Jr. 1966-1967 (Box 14)
  - Darlington School Board of Trustees 1966-1967 (Box 14)
  - Deans Luncheons 1966-1967 (Box 14)
  - Degrees 1966-1967 (Box 14)
  - Duncan, Andrew W. 1966-1967 (Box 14)
  - "E" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 15)
  - Economics 1966-1967 (Box 15)
  - Education - General 1966-1967 (Box 15)
  - Education - Personnel 1966-1967 (Box 15)
  - Education - Rehabilitation Center (see Rehabilitation Center) 1966-1967 (Box 15)
  - Education - Educational Research, Division of (folder empty) 1966-1967 (Box 15)
  - Educational Aid for State Employees 1966-1967 (Box 15)
  - Educational T. V. 1966-1967 (Box 15)
  - Emeriti 1966-1967 (Box 15)
  - Endowment Fund 1966-1967 (Box 15)
  - Engineering - General 1966-1967 (Box 16)
  - Engineering - Personnel 1966-1967 (Box 16)
  - English 1966-1967 (Box 16)
  - Enrollment (see also Registrar) 1966-1967 (Box 16)
  - "F" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 16)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Academic Faculty 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Committees of 1966-1967 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - General 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Personnel, "A - M" 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Personnel, "N - Z" 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Faculty - Five-year Faculty Staffing 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Faculty - General Faculty 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Faculty Orientation and Reception 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Fair Labor Standards Act 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Federal Legislation 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Cross 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - DuPont 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Fulbright 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Love 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Rhodes 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Finals - 1967 1966-1967 (Box 18)
  - Financial Aid to Students, Office of 1966-1967 (Box 18)
  - Ford Foundation 1966-1967 (Box 18)
  - Foreign Student Advisor 1966-1967 (Box 18)
  - Founder's Day 1966-1967 (Box 18)
  - "G" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 19)
  - General Assembly 1966-1967 (Box 19)
  - General Studies 1966-1967 (Box 19)
  - General Studies - personnel 1966-1967 (Box 19)
  - General Studies - Central Virginia Center 1966-1967 (Box 19)
  - General Studies - Eastern Shore Branch 1966-1967 (Box 19)
  - General Studies - Eastern Shore Branch - Personnel 1966-1967 (Box 19)
  - General Studies - Eastern Shore Branch - CONFIDENTIAL - James P. Hanlon 1966-1967 (Box 19)
  - General Studies - Lynchburg Branch 1966-1967 (Box 19)
  - General Studies - Lynchburg Branch - personnel 1966-1967 (Box 19)
  - General Studies - Madison Center 1966-1967 (Box 19)
  - General Studies - Madison Center - personnel 1966-1967 (Box 19)
  - General Studies - Northern Virginia Center 1966-1967 (Box 19)
  - General Studies - Northern Virginia Center - personnel 1966-1967 (Box 19)
  - General Studies - Patrick Henry Branch - Personnel 1966-1967 (Box 19)
  - General Studies - Richmond Center - Personnel 1966-1967 (Box 20)
  - General Studies - Roanoke Center 1966-1967 (Box 20)
  - General Studies - Southwest Virginia Center - Personnel 1966-1967 (Box 20)
  - Geology 1966-1967 (Box 20)
  - George Mason College - July 1966 - December 1966 1966-1967 (Box 20)
  - George Mason College - January 1967 - June 1967 1966-1967 (Box 20)
  - George Mason College - Building Program 1966-1967 (Box 20)
  - George Mason College - Personnel 1966-1967 (Box 20)
  - George Mason College - Recommendations for Director 1966-1967 (Box 20)
  - George Mason College Foundation 1966-1967 (Box 20)
  - Germanic and Slavic Languages, Department of 1966-1967 (Box 21)
  - Government and Foreign Affairs 1966-1967 (Box 21)
  - Governor's Office 1966-1967 (Box 21)
  - Governor's Conference on Education 1966-1967 (Box 21)
  - Graduate Programs 1966-1967 (Box 21)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences 1966-1967 (Box 21)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences - 3-years Master's Degree Program 1966-1967 (Box 21)
  - Graduate Business - Personnel 1966-1967 (Box 21)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration 1966-1967 (Box 21)
  - Graduate School of Business Sponsors 1966-1967 (Box 22)
  - Graduate Program - Master of Arts in Public Administration 1966-1967 (Box 22)
  - Graduate Degree Programs in Tidewater Virginia 1966-1967 (Box 22)
  - Graphics, Department of 1966-1967 (Box 22)
  - Guggenheim Foundation 1966-1967 (Box 22)
  - "H" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 22)
  - Harvard Graduate Society Council 1966-1967 (Box 22)
  - Heald, Hobson and Associates 1966-1967 (Box 23)
  - Higher Education Act 1966-1967 (Box 23)
  - Higher Education Act - Title I 1966-1967 (Box 23)
  - Higher Education Act - Title II 1966-1967 (Box 23)
  - Higher Education Act - Title III 1966-1967 (Box 23)
  - Higher Education Act - Title IV 1966-1967 (Box 23)
  - Higher Education Act - Title V 1966-1967 (Box 23)
  - Higher Education Act - Title VI 1966-1967 (Box 23)
  - Higher Education Study Commission 1966-1967 (Box 23)
  - Highway Department 1966-1967 (Box 23)
  - Historic Lexington Foundation 1966-1967 (Box 23)
  - History 1966-1967 (Box 23)
  - Honor System and Honor Committee 1966-1967 (Box 23)
  - Honors Program 1966-1967 (Box 23)
  - Housing 1966-1967 (Box 23)
  - "I" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 24)
  - Information Services (see Public Relations and Development) 1966-1967 (Box 24)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs 1966-1967 (Box 24)
  - Institute of Early American History and Culture 1966-1967 (Box 24)
  - Institute of Government 1966-1967 (Box 24)
  - Institute of International Education 1966-1967 (Box 24)
  - Institutional Analysis, Office of 1966-1967 (Box 25)
  - Institutional Self-Study 1966-1967 (Box 25)
  - Invitations - "A" 1966-1967 (Box 25)
  - Invitations - "B" 1966-1967 (Box 25)
  - Invitations - "C" 1966-1967 (Box 25)
  - Invitations - "D" 1966-1967 (Box 25)
  - Invitations - "E" 1966-1967 (Box 26)
  - Invitations - "F" 1966-1967 (Box 26)
  - Invitations - "G" 1966-1967 (Box 26)
  - Invitations - "H" 1966-1967 (Box 26)
  - Invitations - "I" 1966-1967 (Box 26)
  - Invitations - "J" 1966-1967 (Box 26)
  - Invitations - "K" 1966-1967 (Box 26)
  - Invitations - "L" 1966-1967 (Box 26)
  - Invitations - "M" 1966-1967 (Box 26)
  - Invitations - "N" 1966-1967 (Box 26)
  - Invitations - "O" 1966-1967 (Box 26)
  - Invitations - "P" 1966-1967 (Box 26)
  - Invitations - "Q" 1966-1967 (Box 26)
  - Invitations - "R" 1966-1967 (Box 26)
  - Invitations - "S" 1966-1967 (Box 27)
  - Invitations - "T" 1966-1967 (Box 27)
  - Invitations - "U" 1966-1967 (Box 27)
  - Invitations - "V" 1966-1967 (Box 27)
  - Invitations - "W" 1966-1967 (Box 27)
  - Invitations - "X - Y - Z" 1966-1967 (Box 27)
  - "J" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 27)
  - Thomas Jefferson Award 1966-1967 (Box 27)
  - Thomas Jefferson Center 1966-1967 (Box 27)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation 1966-1967 (Box 27)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation Board 1966-1967 (Box 27)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Coin Medal 1966-1967 (Box 27)
  - Jefferson Papers 1966-1967 (Box 27)
  - Jefferson Society 1966-1967 (Box 27)
  - "K" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 28)
  - "L" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 28)
  - Law - General 1966-1967 (Box 28)
  - Law - Personnel 1966-1967 (Box 28)
  - Legal 1966-1967 (Box 28)
  - Legal - Estates 1966-1967 (Box 29)
  - Library - Board of Alderman 1966-1967 (Box 29)
  - Library - General 1966-1967 (Box 29)
  - Library - Microfilm Project 1966-1967 (Box 29)
  - "Mc" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 29)
  - "Ma - Me" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 30)
  - "Mi - Mz" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 30)
  - Madison Papers 1966-1967 (Box 30)
  - Marine Science 1966-1967 (Box 31)
  - Mariner's Museum 1966-1967 (Box 31)
  - Markle Foundation 1966-1967 (Box 32)
  - Mary Washington College Folder # 1 1966-1967 (Box 32)
  - Mary Washington College Folder # 2 1966-1967 (Box 32)
  - Mary Washington College Building Program 1966-1967 (Box 32)
  - Mary Washington College Financial 1966-1967 (Box 33)
  - Mary Washington College Personnel 1966-1967 (Box 33)
  - Mathematics 1966-1967 (Box 33)
  - Medical Center - General 1966-1967 (Box 33)
  - Medical Center - Hospital 1966-1967 (Box 33)
  - Medical Center - Hospital Monthly Statistical Reports 1966-1967 (Box 33)
  - Medical Center - Hospital Operating Budget and Reports 1966-1967 (Box 33)
  - Medical Center - Hospital Reports on Current Operations 1966-1967 (Box 33)
  - Medical Center - Medical School Finances 1966-1967 (Box 33)
  - Medical Center - Medical School Personnel 1966-1967 (Box 33)
  - Medical Center - Nursing 1966-1967 (Box 34)
  - Medical Center - Nursing Personnel 1966-1967 (Box 34)
  - Mental Health 1966-1967 (Box 34)
  - Modern Languages 1966-1967 (Box 34)
  - Monroe Foundation and Library 1966-1967 (Box 34)
  - Music 1966-1967 (Box 34)
  - "N" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 34)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges - Folder # 1 1966-1967 (Box 35)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges - Folder # 2 1966-1967 (Box 35)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges - Folder # 3 1966-1967 (Box 36)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges - Circular Letters 1966-1967 (Box 36)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges - Commissions 1966-1967 (Box 37)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges - International Letters 1966-1967 (Box 37)
  - National Commission on Accrediting 1966-1967 (Box 37)
  - National Defense Education Act 1966-1967 (Box 37)
  - National Historical Publications 1966-1967 (Box 38)
  - National Science Foundation 1966-1967 (Box 38)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation 1966-1967 (Box 38)
  - Navy - General 1966-1967 (Box 38)
  - Navy - ROTC 1966-1967 (Box 38)
  - Newcomb Hall (see also Committee on University Union) 1966-1967 (Box 38)
  - Newcomen Society 1966-1967 (Box 38)
  - News Letter 1966-1967 (Box 38)
  - Newspaper Clippings 1966-1967 (Box 38)
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization 1966-1967 (Box 38)
  - "O" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 38)
  - Office - Files 1966-1967 (Box 38)
  - Office - General Stores 1966-1967 (Box 38)
  - Office - Information 1966-1967 (Box 38)
  - Office - Invoices, July - September 1966 1966-1967 (Box 38)
  - Office - Invoices, October - December 1966 1966-1967 (Box 39)
  - Office - Invoices, January - March 1967 1966-1967 (Box 39)
  - Office - Invoices, April - May 1967 1966-1967 (Box 39)
  - Office - Supplies 1966-1967 (Box 39)
  - Office - Travel 1966-1967 (Box 39)
  - Office of Institutional Research 1966-1967 (Box 39)
  - "P - Ph" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 40)
  - "PI - Pz" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 40)
  - Personnel - July - December 1966 1966-1967 (Box 40)
  - Personnel - January - June 1967 1966-1967 (Box 40)
  - Phi Beta Kappa 1966-1967 (Box 40)
  - Philosophy 1966-1967 (Box 40)
  - Photographs 1966-1967 (Box 40)
  - Physics 1966-1967 (Box 40)
  - Planning Department (see also individual building programs) 1966-1967 (Box 40)
  - Project Status Reports 1966-1967 (Box 41)
  - Provost of the University 1966-1967 (Box 41)
  - Psychology 1966-1967 (Box 41)
  - Public Relations 1966-1967 (Box 41)
  - Publications 1966-1967 (Box 41)
  - Purchasing 1966-1967 (Box 41)
  - "Q" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 41)
  - Questionnaires and Inquiries 1966-1967 (Box 41)
  - "R" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 41)
  - Raven Society 1966-1967 (Box 41)
  - Recommendations 1966-1967 (Box 42)
  - Regional Education Laboratory - Central Atlantic 1966-1967 (Box 42)
  - Regional Education Laboratory - Mid-South 1966-1967 (Box 42)
  - Registrar 1966-1967 (Box 42)
  - Registrar - Student Reports 1966-1967 (Box 42)
  - Religion 1966-1967 (Box 42)
  - Religious Organizations - Use of University Facilities 1966-1967 (Box 42)
  - RESEARCH 1966-1967 (Box 42)
  - "S - Sl" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 42)
  - "Sm - Sz" Miscellaneous 1966-1967 (Box 43)
  - Salaries (see also Personnel) 1966-1967 (Box 43)
  - Scholarships (see also Fellowships and Scholarships) 1966-1967 (Box 43)
  - Security, Department of 1966-1967 (Box 43)
  - Senate, University 1966-1967 (Box 43)
  - Senior Scholars Research 1966-1967 (Box 43)
  - Seven Society 1966-1967 (Box 43)
  - Sociology and Anthropology 1966-1967 (Box 43)